Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Adel Bassem Series (Box 2, Box 5)
  - A group portrait of several men with Adel Bassem around a picnic table., Circa 1940-1965; ref251; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.5 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Men; Outdoors; Restaurants/bars; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Jewelry
  - A group portrait of several men with Adel Bassem in suits., Circa 1940-1965; ref252; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 9.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Men; Water; Outdoors; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A group portrait of men with Adel Bassem sitting behind a desk., Circa 1940-1965; ref253; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.2 x 10.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Furnishings; Men; Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of several men with Adel Bassem outdoors., Circa 1940-1965; ref254; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Streets/Roads
  - A portrait of a man in a shop., Circa 1940-1965; ref255; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.5 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Men; Shops; Tea/Coffee; Clocks/Watches; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait with double exposure of men wearing suits outdoors., Circa 1935-1950; ref256; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Men; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Waterfalls
  - A group portrait of men swimming and holding tree branches., Circa 1935-1950; ref257; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.8 x 11 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Swimming; Water; Men; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A team portrait with the coach Adel Bassem on a field., Circa 1965-1980; ref258; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Sports; Football; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Arabic Writing; Boys; Children; Men
  - A group portrait of three men with a waterfall in the background., Circa 1935-1950; ref259; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Men; Waterfalls; Outdoors; Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of six men with Adel Bassem near water., Circa 1940-1965; ref260; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Water; Clocks/Watches
  - A team portrait with the coach, Adel Bassem., Circa 1965-1980; ref261; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Sports; Outdoors; Men; Boys; Photographic Prints; Syria; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children
  - A group portrait of three men in the water., Circa 1940-1965; ref262; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.5 x 6.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Water; Swimming; Mountains/Hills; Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A portrait of a man and a horse outdoors., Circa 1940-1965; ref263; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 4.4 x 5.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Horses; Animals; Outdoors; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and two men with trophies., Circa 1940-1965; ref264; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Arabic Writing; Awards; Facial Hair; Furnishings
  - A group portrait of men, including Adel Bassem, eating food outdoors., Circa 1940-1965; ref265; Tirage Photo Dadour, Alep (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Men; Picnic; Food; Outdoors; Uniforms; Gatherings; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Military/Soldiers; Facial Hair; Forest/Woodlands
  - A portrait of a men in an amphitheater., Circa 1940-1965; ref266; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Syria; Architecture; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A large group portrait of men, women, and children., Circa 1940-1965; ref267; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Women; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Facial Hair; Boys; Girls
  - A group portrait of men indoors with Adel Bassem., Circa 1940-1965; ref268; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.5 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Clocks/Watches; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
  - A team portrait with two balls., Circa 1965-1980; ref269; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Boys; Children; Football; Sports; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of four men, three are wearing jerseys., Circa 1965-1980; ref270; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Sports; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of two men with Adel Bassem wearing sports attire., Circa 1965-1980; ref271; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 x 8.7 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem wearing sports attire with two other men., Circa 1940-1965; ref272; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of Adel Bassem using gymnastic rings., Circa 1950-1965; ref273; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Sports; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Furnishings; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of a topless Adel Bassem., Circa 1930-1950; ref274; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 6.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Individual Portraits; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hats; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A full-body portrait of Adel Bassem flexing., Circa 1930-1950; ref275; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Men; Outdoors; Hats; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and five other men., Circa 1940-1965; ref276; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Men; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of Adel Bassem and a little girl holding a weight., Circa 1940-1965; ref277; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Men; Girls; Children; Sports; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Jewelry
  - A group portrait of topless men and children, including Adel Bassem., Circa 1940-1965; ref278; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 13.7 cm (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Children; Boys; Men; Syria; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Sports; Facial Hair; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Swimming Pools; Hats
  - A group portrait of several men wearing sports vests., 26 August 1977; ref279; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 13.3. cm (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Children; Boys; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of a man lifting a barbell with others in the background., Circa 1940-1965; ref280; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Syria; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of two topless men with Adel Bassem flexing outdoors., Circa 1930-1950; ref281; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 9.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and two men with buildings in the background., Circa 1930-1950; ref282; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.3 x 10.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Arabic Writing; Syria; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Facial Hair; Buildings
  - A group portrait of four topless men flexing., 8 June 1961; ref283; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Syria; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports
  - A group portrait of men playing tug-of-war., Circa 1940-1965; ref284; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.2 x 7.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Outdoors; Sports; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A portrait of Adel Bassem in his sports attire., Circa 1940-1965; ref285; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.6 x 6.1 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Sports; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and two topless men., Circa 1940-1965; ref286; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 8.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of a man flexing in front of a building., Circa 1940-1965; ref287; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of a man flexing with Adel Bassem., Circa 1940-1965; ref288; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.3 x 5.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Sports; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of Adel Bassem flexing., Circa 1940-1965; ref289; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 8.7 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Syria; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of Adel Bassem flexing., Circa 1940-1965; ref290; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 x 8.7 cm (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Sports; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and three men with plants., 28 August 1963; ref291; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 8.9 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair
  - A team portrait with a coach, Adel Bassem, taken outdoors., Circa 1965-1980; ref292; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.7 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Men; Sports; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Outdoors
  - A portrait of a man in a suit outdoors., Circa 1940-1965; ref293; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.2 x 6.4 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Men; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of two boys in sports attire outside (linked ref 295)., Circa 1960-1980; ref294; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 5.2 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Boys; Children; Sports; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of two boys in sports attire outside (linked ref 294)., Circa 1960-1980; ref295; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Boys; Children; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports
  - A team portrait with a coach, Adel Bassem, taken outdoors., Circa 1960-1980; ref296; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.8 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Men; Boys; Children; Syria; Sports; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of men with Adel Bassem in a waterfront building., Circa 1940-1965; ref297; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Men; Regional/National Dress; Syria; Water; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of three men, two are wearing sports attire., Circa 1960-1980; ref298; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Men; Outdoors; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A portrait of Adel Bassem wearing a uniform., Circa 1960-1980; ref299; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6.1 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Uniforms; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of men standing on a terrace., Circa 1960-1980; ref300; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Buildings
  - A group portrait of men in suits with a field in the background., 12 June 1960; ref301; Studio Venge, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Men; Stadiums; Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and other men in front of running water., Circa 1960-1980; ref302; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Men; Outdoors; Water; Waterfalls; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of seven men in an outdoor restaurant., Circa 1950-1980; ref303; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.4 x 10.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Men; Restaurants/bars; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tea/Coffee; Fezes/Tarbouches; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and seven other men., Circa 1940-1965; ref304; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.5 x 10.6 cm (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Men; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A group portrait several of men in suits standing outdoors., Circa 1940-1965; ref305; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Men; Palm Trees; Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Facial Hair; Hats; Palm Trees; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A portrait of a man holding a railing with two other men., Circa 1940-1965; ref306; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.5 cm (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Men; Boats/Ships; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem speaking with another man., Circa 1940-1965; ref782; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Syria; Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
  - An individual portrait of a body builder., Circa 1940-1965; ref783; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Sports; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - An individual portrait of a body builder., Circa 1940-1965; ref784; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Men; Sports; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
  - An individual portrait of a body builder., Circa 1940-1965; ref785; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Arabic Calligraphy; Men; Sports; Syria; Individual Portraits
  - An individual portrait of a body builder., Circa 1940-1965; ref786; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Men; Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a body builder on a magazine cover., Circa 1940-1965; ref787; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Newspapers/Magazines; Men; Sports; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a body builder (linked ref 789)., Circa 1940-1965; ref788; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Men; Sports; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a body builder (linked ref 788)., Circa 1940-1965; ref789; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Individual Portraits; Men; Syria; Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of three body builders outside., Circa 1940-1965; ref790; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Men; Sports; Syria; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a body builder outdoors., Circa 1950-1975; ref791; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Men; Sports; Syria; Forest/Woodlands; Outdoors; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of Mr. Mahdy Kanza Mustafa, one of Baghdad's body building champions., Circa 1950-1975; ref792; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Baghdad, Iraq; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints
  - An individual portrait of a young man flexing., Circa 1950-1975; ref793; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - An individual portrait of a man in a swimming pool., Circa 1950-1975; ref794; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Syria; Swimming Pools; Swimming; Photographic Prints; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - An individual portrait of a body builder, Saeed Nassar, outdoors., Circa 1950-1975; ref795; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Sports; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - An individual portrait of a body builder on a magazine cover., Circa 1950-1975; ref796; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Syria; Newspapers/Magazines; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Sports; Men
  - An individual portrait of a body builder on a magazine cover., Circa 1950-1975; ref797; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Sports; Individual Portraits; Newspapers/Magazines; Damascus, Syria
  - An individual portrait of a body builder holding a sword., Circa 1950-1975; ref798; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Damascus, Syria
  - An individual portrait of a body builder on a Muscle Magazine cover., Circa 1950-1975; ref799; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Sports; Newspapers/Magazines; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of three body builders receiving awards at a competition., Circa 1950-1975; ref800; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Awards; Sports; Group Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A studio portrait of a body builder flexing., Circa 1950-1975; ref801; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Men; Sports; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and several men sitting in the desert., Circa 1960-1980; ref802; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Men; Deserts; Picnic; Group Portraits; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of Adel bassem in a kitchen with two men., Circa 1960-1980; ref803; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Syria
  - An individual portrait of Adel bassem sitting at a table., Circa 1960-1980; ref804; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Men; Radios; Individual Portraits; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - An individual portrait of a man raising his hand at a swimming pool., Circa 1960-1980; ref805; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 8.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Men; Swimming Pools; Mountains/Hills; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A parade float decorated with flowers with women walking at its side., Circa 1960-1980; ref806; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Parades/Processions; Cars/Trucks; Women; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Syria; Color Photography; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and two other men in front of a car., Circa 1960-1980; ref807; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Cars/Trucks; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of Adel Bassem and four other men surrounded by trophies., Circa 1960-1980; ref808; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Syria; Color Photography; Photographic Prints
  - An individual portrait of a boxer., Circa 1960-1980; ref809; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Men; Sports; Gloves; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - An individual portrait of a man jumping off a diving board., Circa 1960-1980; ref810; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Swimming Pools; Men; Individual Portraits; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A team portrait with Adel Bassem., Circa 1960-1980; ref811; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.6 x 8.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Sports; Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A team portrait with Adel Bassem taken outdoors., Circa 1960-1980; ref812; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 9 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Men; Sports; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Color Photography
  - A group portrait of several men jumping off diving boards into a pool., Circa 1960-1980; ref813; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Swimming Pools; Men; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Photographic Prints
  - A team portrait of several boys with Adel Bassem., 26 August 1977; ref814; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.9 x 8.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Sports; Men; Boys; Children
  - A team portrait taken on a field., Circa 1960-1975; ref858; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.7 cm (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Men; Sports; Group Portraits; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men around a trophy (linked ref860)., Circa 1960-1975; ref859; Studio Georges Derzi, Press Photography Department, Salhieh, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.5 x 12.3 cm (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Men; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Crowds; Syria; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints